[{"question":"# Q1. Given the string \"strawberries\" saved in a variable called fruit, what would `fruit.substring(2, 5)` return?","options":["rawb","raw","awb","traw","**Reasoning:** The substring method is accepting two arguments. The first argument being the index to start(includes that char at 2) and the second the index of the string to end the substring(excludes the char at 5). Strings in Java are like arrays of chars. Therefore the method will return \"raw\" as those are the chars in indexes 2,3, and 4. You can also take the ending index and subtract the beginning index from it, to determine how many chars will be included in the substring (5-2=3)."],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"raw"},{"question":"# Q2. How can you achieve runtime polymorphism in Java?","options":["method overloading","method overrunning","method overriding","method calling"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"method overriding"},{"question":"# Q3. Given the following definitions, which of these expression will **NOT** evaluate to true?","options":["boolean b1 = true, b2 = false; int i1 = 1, i2 = 2;","(i1 | i2) == 3","i2 && b1","b1 || !b2","(i1 ^ i2) < 4"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"i2 && b1"},{"question":"# Q4. What can you use to create new instances in Java?","options":["constructor","another instance","field","private method"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"constructor"},{"question":"# Q5. What is the output of this code?\n\n```shell\n1: class Main {\n2:   public static void main (String[] args) {\n3:     int array[] = {1, 2, 3, 4};\n4:     for (int i = 0; i < array.size(); i++) {\n5:        System.out.print(array[i]);\n6:     }\n7:   }\n8: }\n\n```","options":["It will not compile because of line 4.","It will not compile because of line 3.","123","1234"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"It will not compile because of line 4."},{"question":"# Q6. Which of the following can replace the CODE SNIPPET to make the code below print \"Hello World\"?\n\n```java\ninterface Interface1 {\n    static void print() {\n        System.out.print(\"Hello\");\n    }\n}\n\ninterface Interface2 {\n    static void print() {\n        System.out.print(\"World!\");\n    }\n}\n\n```","options":["super1.print(); super2.print();","this.print();","super.print();","Interface1.print(); Interface2.print();"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"Interface1.print(); Interface2.print();"},{"question":"# Q7. What does the following code print?\n\n```java\nString str = \"abcde\";\nstr.trim();\nstr.toUpperCase();\nstr.substring(3, 4);\nSystem.out.println(str);\n\n```","options":["CD","CDE","D","\"abcde\""],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"\"abcde\""},{"question":"# Q8. What is the result of this code?\n\n```java\nclass Main {\n    public static void main (String[] args){\n        System.out.println(print(1));\n    }\n    static Exception print(int i){\n        if (i>0) {\n            return new Exception();\n        } else {\n            throw new RuntimeException();\n        }\n    }\n}\n\n```","options":["It will show a stack trace with a runtime exception.","\"java.lang.Exception\"","It will run and throw an exception.","It will not compile."],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"\"java.lang.Exception\""},{"question":"# Q9. Which class can compile given these declarations?\n\n```java\ninterface One {\n    default void method() {\n        System.out.println(\"\"One\"\");\n    }\n}\n\ninterface Two {\n    default void method () {\n        System.out.println(\"\"One\"\");\n    }\n}\n\n```","options":["A"]},{"question":"# Q10. What is the output of this code?\n\n```java\nclass Main {\n    public static void main (String[] args) {\n        List list = new ArrayList();\n        list.add(\"hello\");\n        list.add(2);\n        System.out.print(list.get(0) instanceof Object);\n        System.out.print(list.get(1) instanceof Integer);\n    }\n}\n\n```","options":["The code does not compile.","truefalse","truetrue","falsetrue"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"truetrue"},{"question":"# Q11. Given the following two classes, what will be the output of the Main class?\n\n```java\npackage mypackage;\npublic class Math {\n    public static int abs(int num){\n        return num < 0 ? -num : num;\n    }\n}\npackage mypackage.elementary;\npublic class Math {\n    public static int abs (int num) {\n        return -num;\n    }\n}\n\n```","options":[]},{"question":"# Q12. What is the result of this code?\n\n```java\n1: class MainClass {\n2:  final String message(){\n3:      return \"Hello!\";\n4:  }\n5: }\n\n6: class Main extends MainClass {\n7:  public static void main(String[] args) {\n8:      System.out.println(message());\n9:  }\n\n10: String message(){\n11:     return \"World!\";\n12:  }\n13: }\n\n```","options":["It will not compile because of line 10.","\"Hello!\"","It will not compile because of line 2.","\"World!\"","**Explanation:** Non-static method message() cannot be referenced from a static context."],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"It will not compile because of line 10."},{"question":"# Q13. Given this code, which command will output \"2\"?\n\n```java\nclass Main {\n    public static void main(String[] args) {\n        System.out.println(args[2]);\n    }\n}\n\n```","options":["java Main 1 2 \"3 4\" 5","java Main 1 \"2\" \"2\" 5","java Main.class 1 \"2\" 2 5","java Main 1 \"2\" \"3 4\" 5"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"java Main 1 \"2\" \"2\" 5"},{"question":"# Q14. What is the output of this code?\n\n```java\nclass Main {\n    public static void main(String[] args){\n        int a = 123451234512345;\n        System.out.println(a);\n    }\n}\n\n```","options":["\"123451234512345\"","Nothing - this will not compile.","a negative integer value","\"12345100000\"","**Reasoning:** The int type in Java can be used to represent any whole number from -2147483648 to 2147483647. Therefore this code will not compile as the number assigned to 'a' is larger than the int type can hold."],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"Nothing - this will not compile."},{"question":"# Q15. What is the output of this code?\n\n```java\nclass Main {\n    public static void main (String[] args) {\n        String message = \"Hello world!\";\n        String newMessage = message.substring(6, 12)\n            + message.substring(12, 6);\n        System.out.println(newMessage);\n    }\n}\n\n```","options":["The code does not compile.","A runtime exception is thrown.","\"world!!world\"","\"world!world!\""],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"A runtime exception is thrown."},{"question":"# Q16. How do you write a foreach loop that will iterate over ArrayList\\<Pencil\\>pencilCase?","options":["for (Pencil pencil : pencilCase) {}","for (pencilCase.next()) {}","for (Pencil pencil : pencilCase.iterator()) {}","for (pencil in pencilCase) {}"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"for (Pencil pencil : pencilCase) {}"},{"question":"# Q17. Fill in the blanks?","options":["- Object-oriented programming (OOP) is a programming language model that organizes software design around (objects), rather than (actions)."]},{"question":"# Q18. What code would you use to tell if \"schwifty\" is of type String?","options":["\"schwifty\".getType() == String","\"schwifty\".getClass().getSimpleName() == \"String\"","\"schwifty\".getType().equals(\"String\")","\"schwifty\" instanceof String"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"\"schwifty\" instanceof String"},{"question":"# Q19. What does this code print?\n\n```java\nSystem.out.print(\"apple\".compareTo(\"banana\"));\n\n```","options":["0","positive number","negative number","compilation error"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"negative number"},{"question":"# Q20. You have an ArrayList of names that you want to sort alphabetically. Which approach would **NOT** work?","options":["names.sort(Comparator.comparing(String::toString))","Collections.sort(names)","names.sort(List.DESCENDING)","names.stream().sorted((s1, s2) -> s1.compareTo(s2)).collect(Collectors.toList())"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"names.sort(List.DESCENDING)"},{"question":"# Q21. By implementing encapsulation, you cannot directly access the class's **\\_** properties unless you are writing code inside the class itself.","options":["private","protected","no-modifier","public"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"private"},{"question":"# Q22. Which is the most up-to-date way to instantiate the current date?","options":["new SimpleDateFormat(\"yyyy-MM-dd\").format(new Date())","new Date(System.currentTimeMillis())","LocalDate.now()","Calendar.getInstance().getTime()","**Explanation**: LocalDate is newest class added in java 8"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"LocalDate.now()"},{"question":"# Q23. Fill in the blank to create a piece of code that will tell wether int0 is divisible by 5:","options":["boolean isDivisibleBy5 = _____","int0 / 5 ? true: false","int0 % 5 == 0","int0 % 5 != 5","Math.isDivisible(int0, 5)"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"int0 % 5 == 0"},{"question":"# Q24. How many times will this code print \"Hello World!\"?\n\n```java\nclass Main {\n    public static void main(String[] args){\n        for (int i=0; i<10; i=i++){\n            i+=1;\n            System.out.println(\"Hello World!\");\n        }\n    }\n}\n\n```","options":["10 times","9 times","5 times","infinite number of times","Reason : Observe the loop increment. It's not an increment, it's an assignment(post)."],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"10 times"},{"question":"# Q25. The runtime system starts your program by calling which function first?","options":["print","iterative","hello","main"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"main"},{"question":"# Q26. What is the result of this code?\n\n```java\ntry{\n    System.out.print(\"Hello World\");\n}catch(Exception e){\n    System.out.println(\"e\");\n}catch(ArithmeticException e){\n    System.out.println(\"e\");\n}finally{\n    System.out.println(\"!\")\n}\n\n```","options":["It will throw a runtime exception","It will not compile","Hello World!","Hello World"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"It will not compile"},{"question":"# Q27. Which statement is **NOT** true?","options":["An anonymous class may specify an abstract base class as its base type.","An anonymous class does not require a zero-argument constructor.","An anonymous class may specify an interface as its base type.","An anonymous class may specify both an abstract class and interface as base types."],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"An anonymous class does not require a zero-argument constructor."},{"question":"# Q28. What will this program print out to the console when executed?\n\n```java\nimport java.util.LinkedList;\n\npublic class Main {\n    public static void main(String[] args){\n        LinkedList<Integer> list = new LinkedList<>();\n        list.add(5);\n        list.add(1);\n        list.add(10);\n        System.out.println(list);\n    }\n}\n\n```","options":["[5, 1, 10]","[10, 5, 1]","[1, 5, 10]","[10, 1, 5]"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"[5, 1, 10]"},{"question":"# Q29. What is the output of this code?\n\n```java\nclass Main {\n    public static void main(String[] args){\n       String message = \"Hello\";\n       for (int i = 0; i<message.length(); i++){\n          System.out.print(message.charAt(i+1));\n       }\n    }\n}\n\n```","options":["\"Hello\"","A runtime exception is thrown.","The code does not compile.","\"ello\""],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"A runtime exception is thrown."},{"question":"# Q30. Object-oriented programming is a style of programming where you organize your program around \\_**\\_ rather than \\_\\_** and data rather than logic.","options":["functions; actions","objects; actions","actions; functions","actions; objects"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"objects; actions"},{"question":"# Q31. What statement returns true if \"nifty\" is of type String?","options":["\"nifty\".getType().equals(\"String\")","\"nifty\".getType() == String","\"nifty\".getClass().getSimpleName() == \"String\"","\"nifty\" instanceof String"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"\"nifty\" instanceof String"},{"question":"# Q32. What is the output of this code?\n\n```java\nimport java.util.*;\nclass Main {\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args) {\n\t\tList<Boolean> list = new ArrayList<>();\n\t\tlist.add(true);\n\t\tlist.add(Boolean.parseBoolean(\"FalSe\"));\n\t\tlist.add(Boolean.TRUE);\n\t\tSystem.out.print(list.size());\n\t\tSystem.out.print(list.get(1) instanceof Boolean);\n\t}\n}\n\n```","options":["A runtime exception is thrown.","3false","2true","3true"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"3true"},{"question":"# Q33. What is the result of this code?\n\n```java\n1: class Main {\n2: \t\tObject message(){\n3: \t\t\treturn \"Hello!\";\n4: \t\t}\n5: \t\tpublic static void main(String[] args) {\n6: \t\t\tSystem.out.print(new Main().message());\n7: \t\t\tSystem.out.print(new Main2().message());\n8: \t\t}\n9: }\n10: class Main2 extends Main {\n11: \tString message(){\n12: \t\treturn \"World!\";\n13: \t}\n14: }\n\n```","options":["It will not compile because of line 7.","Hello!Hello!","Hello!World!","It will not compile because of line 11."],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"Hello!World!"},{"question":"# Q34. What method can be used to create a new instance of an object?","options":["another instance","field","constructor","private method"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"constructor"},{"question":"# Q35. Which is the most reliable expression for testing whether the values of two string variables are the same?","options":["string1 == string2","string1 = string2","string1.matches(string2)","string1.equals(string2)"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"string1.equals(string2)"},{"question":"# Q36. Which letters will print when this code is run?\n\n```java\npublic static void main(String[] args) {\n\ttry {\n\t\tSystem.out.println(\"A\");\n\t\tbadMethod();\n\t\tSystem.out.println(\"B\");\n\t} catch (Exception ex) {\n\t\tSystem.out.println(\"C\");\n\t} finally {\n\t\tSystem.out.println(\"D\");\n\t}\n}\npublic static void badMethod() {\n\tthrow new Error();\n}\n\n```","options":["A, B, and D","A, C, and D","C and D","A and D"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"A and D"},{"question":"# Q37. What is the output of this code?\n\n```java\nclass Main {\n\tstatic int count = 0;\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args) {\n\t\tif (count < 3) {\n\t\t\tcount++;\n\t\t\tmain(null);\n\t\t} else {\n\t\t\treturn;\n\t\t}\n\t\tSystem.out.println(\"Hello World!\");\n\t}\n}\n\n```","options":["It will throw a runtime exception.","It will not compile.","It will print \"Hello World!\" three times.","It will run forever."],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"It will print \"Hello World!\" three times."},{"question":"# Q38. What is the output of this code?\n\n```java\nimport java.util.*;\nclass Main {\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args) {\n\t\tString[] array = {\"abc\", \"2\", \"10\", \"0\"};\n\t\tList<String> list = Arrays.asList(array);\n\t\tCollections.sort(list);\n\t\tSystem.out.println(Arrays.toString(array));\n\t}\n}\n\n```","options":["[abc, 0, 2, 10]","The code does not compile.","[abc, 2, 10, 0]","[0, 10, 2, abc]"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"[0, 10, 2, abc]"},{"question":"# Q39. What is the output of this code?\n\n```java\nclass Main {\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args) {\n\t\tString message = \"Hello\";\n\t\tprint(message);\n\t\tmessage += \"World!\";\n\t\tprint(message);\n\t}\n\tstatic void print(String message){\n\t\tSystem.out.print(message);\n\t\tmessage += \" \";\n\t}\n}\n\n```","options":["Hello World!","HelloHelloWorld!","Hello Hello World!","Hello HelloWorld!"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"HelloHelloWorld!"},{"question":"# Q40. What is displayed when this code is compiled and executed?\n\n```java\npublic class Main {\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args) {\n\t\tint x = 5;\n\t\tx = 10;\n\t\tSystem.out.println(x);\n\t}\n}\n\n```","options":["x","null","10","5"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"10"},{"question":"# Q41. Which approach cannot be used to iterate over a List named _theList_?\n\n- [ ] A\n\n```java\nfor (int i = 0; i < theList.size(); i++) {\n    System.out.println(theList.get(i));\n}\n\n```","options":["B"]},{"question":"# Q42. What method signature will work with this code?","options":["boolean healthyOrNot = isHealthy(\"avocado\");","public void isHealthy(String avocado)","boolean isHealthy(String string)","public isHealthy(\"avocado\")","private String isHealthy(String food)"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"boolean isHealthy(String string)"},{"question":"# Q43. Which are valid keywords in a Java module descriptor (module-infoJava)?","options":["provides, employs","imports, exports","consumes, supplies","requires, exports"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"requires, exports"},{"question":"# Q44. Which type of variable keeps a constant value once it is assigned?","options":["non-static","static","final","private"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"final"},{"question":"# Q45. How does the keyword `_volatile_` affect how a variable is handled?","options":["It will be read by only one thread at a time.","It will be stored on the hard drive.","It will never be cached by the CPU.","It will be preferentially garbage collected."],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"It will never be cached by the CPU."},{"question":"# Q46. What is the result of this code?\n\n```java\nchar smooch = 'x';\nSystem.out.println((int) smooch);\n\n```","options":["an alphanumeric character","a negative number","a positive number","a ClassCastException"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"a positive number"},{"question":"# Q47. You get a NullPointerException. What is the most likely cause?","options":["A file that needs to be opened cannot be found.","A network connection has been lost in the middle of communications.","Your code has used up all available memory.","The object you are using has not been instantiated."],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"The object you are using has not been instantiated."},{"question":"# Q48. How would you fix this code so that it compiles?\n\n```java\npublic class Nosey {\n\tint age;\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args) {\n\t\tSystem.out.println(\"Your age is: \" + age);\n\t}\n}\n\n```","options":["Make age static.","Make age global.","Make age public.","Initialize age to a number."],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"Make age static."},{"question":"# Q49. Add a Duck called \"Waddles\" to the ArrayList **ducks**.\n\n```java\npublic class Duck {\n\tprivate String name;\n\tDuck(String name) {}\n}\n\n```","options":["Duck waddles = new Duck();","      `ducks.add(waddles);","Duck duck = new Duck(\"Waddles\");","      `ducks.add(waddles);","ducks.add(new Duck(\"Waddles\"));","ducks.add(new Waddles());"],"anwserIndex":4,"answerText":"ducks.add(new Duck(\"Waddles\"));"},{"question":"# Q50. If you encounter `UnsupportedClassVersionError` it means the code was `**\\_**` on a newer version of Java than the JRE `**\\_**` it.","options":["executed; interpreting","executed; compiling","compiled; executing","compiled, translating"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"compiled; executing"},{"question":"# Q51. Given this class, how would you make the code compile?\n\n```java\npublic class TheClass {\n    private final int x;\n}\n\n```","options":["A"]},{"question":"# Q52. How many times f will be printed?\n\n```java\npublic class Solution {\n    public static void main(String[] args) {\n        for (int i = 44; i > 40; i--) {\n            System.out.println(\"f\");\n        }\n    }\n}\n\n```","options":["4","3","5","A Runtime exception will be thrown"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"4"},{"question":"# Q53. Which statements about `abstract` classes are true?\n\n```\n1. They can be instantiated.\n2. They allow member variables and methods to be inherited by subclasses.\n3. They can contain constructors.\n\n```","options":["1, 2, and 3","only 3","2 and 3","only 2"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"2 and 3"},{"question":"# Q54. Which keyword lets you call the constructor of a parent class?","options":["parent","super","this","new"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"super"},{"question":"# Q55. What is the result of this code?\n\n```java\n  1: int a = 1;\n  2: int b = 0;\n  3: int c = a/b;\n  4: System.out.println(c);\n\n```","options":["It will throw an ArithmeticException.","It will run and output 0.","It will not compile because of line 3.","It will run and output infinity."],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"It will throw an ArithmeticException."},{"question":"# Q56. Normally, to access a static member of a class such as Math.PI, you would need to specify the class \"Math\". What would be the best way to allow you to use simply \"PI\" in your code?","options":["Add a static import.","Declare local copies of the constant in your code.","This cannot be done. You must always qualify references to static members with the class form which they came from.","Put the static members in an interface and inherit from that interface."],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"Add a static import."},{"question":"# Q57. Which keyword lets you use an interface?","options":["extends","implements","inherits","import"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"implements"},{"question":"# Q58. Why are ArrayLists better than arrays?","options":["You don't have to decide the size of an ArrayList when you first make it.","You can put more items into an ArrayList than into an array.","ArrayLists can hold more kinds of objects than arrays.","You don't have to decide the type of an ArrayList when you first make it."],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"You don't have to decide the size of an ArrayList when you first make it."},{"question":"# Q59. Declare a variable that holds the first four digits of Π","options":["int pi = 3.141;","decimal pi = 3.141;","double pi = 3.141;","float pi = 3.141;"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"float pi = 3.141;"},{"question":"# Q60. Use the magic power to cast a spell\n\n```java\npublic class MagicPower {\n    void castSpell(String spell) {}\n}\n\n```","options":["new MagicPower().castSpell(\"expecto patronum\")","MagicPower magicPower = new MagicPower();","      `magicPower.castSpell();","MagicPower.castSpell(\"expelliarmus\");","new MagicPower.castSpell();"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"new MagicPower().castSpell(\"expecto patronum\")"},{"question":"# Q61. What language construct serves as a blueprint containing an object's properties and functionality?","options":["constructor","instance","class","method"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"class"},{"question":"# Q62. What does this code print?\n\n```java\npublic static void main(String[] args) {\n    int x=5,y=10;\n    swapsies(x,y);\n    System.out.println(x+\"=\"+y);\n}\n\nstatic void swapsies(int a, int b) {\n    int temp=a;\n    a=b;\n    b=temp;\n}\n\n```","options":["10=10","5=10","10=5","5=5"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"5=10"},{"question":"# Q63. What is the result of this code?\n\n```java\ntry {\n    System.out.println(\"Hello World\");\n} catch (Exception e) {\n    System.out.println(\"e\");\n} catch (ArithmeticException e) {\n    System.out.println(\"e\");\n} finally {\n    System.out.println(\"!\");\n}\n\n```","options":["Hello World","It will not compile because the second catch statement is unreachable","Hello World!","It will throw runtime exception"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"It will not compile because the second catch statement is unreachable"},{"question":"# Q64. What is not a java keyword","options":["finally","native","interface","unsigned"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"unsigned"},{"question":"# Q65. Which operator would you use to find the remainder after division?","options":["%","//","/","DIV","[Reference](http://www.cs.ukzn.ac.za/~hughm/java/intro/week2/21.html)"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"%"},{"question":"# Q66. Which choice is a disadvantage of inheritance?","options":["Overridden methods of the parent class cannot be reused.","Responsibilities are not evenly distributed between parent and child classes.","Classes related by inheritance are tightly coupled to each other.","The internal state of the parent class is accessible to its children.","[Reference](http://erpbasic.blogspot.com/2012/01/inheritance-advantages-and.html#:~:text=Main%20disadvantage%20of%20using%20inheritance,used%20independent%20of%20each%20other.&text=4.,case%20of%20using%20that%20method.)"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"Classes related by inheritance are tightly coupled to each other."},{"question":"# Q67. Declare and initialize an array of 10 ints.","options":["Array<Integer> numbers = new Array<Integer>(10);","Array[int] numbers = new Array[int](10);","int[] numbers = new int[10];","int numbers[] = int[10];"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"int[] numbers = new int[10];"},{"question":"# Q68. Refactor this event handler to a lambda expression:\n\n```java\ngroucyButton.addActionListener(new ActionListener() {\n    @Override\n    public void actionPerformed(ActionEvent e) {\n        System.out.println(\"Press me one more time..\");\n    }\n});\n\n```","options":["groucyButton.addActionListener(ActionListener listener -> System.out.println(\"Press me one more time...\"));","groucyButton.addActionListener((event) -> System.out.println(\"Press me one more time...\"));","groucyButton.addActionListener(new ActionListener(ActionEvent e) {() -> System.out.println(\"Press me one more time...\");});","groucyButton.addActionListener(() -> System.out.println(\"Press me one more time...\"));","[Reference](https://www.codejava.net/java-core/the-java-language/java-8-lambda-listener-example)"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"groucyButton.addActionListener((event) -> System.out.println(\"Press me one more time...\"));"},{"question":"# Q69. Which functional interfaces does Java provide to serve as data types for lambda expressions?","options":["Observer, Observable","Collector, Builder","Filter, Map, Reduce","Consumer, Predicate, Supplier","[Reference](https://www.baeldung.com/java-8-functional-interfaces)"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"Consumer, Predicate, Supplier"}]